<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Up Skill on Naresh Chaurasia</title>
    <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Up Skill on Naresh Chaurasia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 15:53:08 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Journaling</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/journaling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 15:53:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/journaling/</guid>
      <description> Exercise 2  Becoming Your Life’s Historian Documenting Lessons Learned Chronicling Your Dreams Morning Pages and Getting It All Out Your Daily &amp;ldquo;Why&amp;rdquo; Goals, To-Do&amp;rsquo;s, and Progress Tracking Gratitude Journaling Gratitude Journaling Training Your Want Muscle    This page will server as a template for Journaling. It will contain structure to write daily, weekly, montly, yearly and life time Journaling.
Exercise 2 Becoming Your Life’s Historian  Things you’re working on Relationships New experiences Recent &amp;ldquo;wins&amp;rdquo; Mistakes or missteps Current emotional state How you’re spending time Who you’re surrounded by What you’re planning  Documenting Lessons Learned  &amp;ldquo;Yesterday (or today) I learned…&amp;rdquo;  Chronicling Your Dreams  Describe your dreams Keep journal on bedside table  Morning Pages and Getting It All Out  3 pages of freestyle writing No theme or structure No filters  Your Daily &amp;ldquo;Why&amp;rdquo;  My &amp;lsquo;why&amp;rsquo; for today is… Higher purpose for today&amp;rsquo;s actions  Goals, To-Do&amp;rsquo;s, and Progress Tracking  Today’s 2-3 &amp;ldquo;crucial results&amp;rdquo; Tracking daily habit compliance  Gratitude Journaling  I&amp;rsquo;m grateful for… As many items as you can As detailed as possible  Gratitude Journaling  I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to… As many items as you can As detailed as possible  Training Your Want Muscle  I want… Dream as big as you can Avoid shallow wants  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Da Vinci Resolve</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/da-vinci-resolve/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 11:02:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/da-vinci-resolve/</guid>
      <description> Features of Da Vinci Resolve Short Cuts  Features of Da Vinci Resolve  Rearrange / Reshuffle clips in timeline Overwrite Clips. Not recommended to use Once we have dropped the video on time line, we can change the in point and out point using the ripple trimming.  Short Cuts </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marathi</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/marathi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 11:02:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/marathi/</guid>
      <description>Day 1 Day 2 Day 3  Day 1   My Name is Naresh: माझे नाव नरेश आहे
  I live in Pune: मी पुण्यात राहतो
  I am engineer: मी इंजीनियर आहे
  I work at Cognizant: मी Cognizant मध्ये/Madhe (में) Job करतो
  I am a native of MP: Me Mulcha MPcha aahe
   माझा (mAjhA ) for masculine, माझी (mAjhI ) for feminine, माझे (mAjhe) for neuter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Templates</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 11:02:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/templates/</guid>
      <description> Technical Template  Sergey Kargopolov Case Study    I need to build / design a system for my learning. This system will be built using inputs from different sources (Udemy, Pluralsight, JIRA etc.)
Technical Template Sergey Kargopolov Case Study  GAPP System from Himesh Trivedi Jonathan Levi Techniques   </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOGAF</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/togaf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 11:02:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/togaf/</guid>
      <description>Jonathan Levi  07.05.2022  This might sound crazy but at least I am able to remember abstract information. Wow !!! It&amp;rsquo;s working    </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>