<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dance on Naresh Chaurasia</title>
    <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/dance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dance on Naresh Chaurasia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:23:01 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/dance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bachata</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/dance/bachata/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:23:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/dance/bachata/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kizomba</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/dance/kizomba/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:23:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/dance/kizomba/</guid>
      <description>Kozomba on Fire Kizomba Steps  Kozomba on Fire Taraxa V/s Kizomba
So taraxa is slow movements the wave movements that lady moving the hips. And when you are very slowly dancing with your lady or with your partner because the music is smooth there are not many strong beats.
Wave - 1 Movement Taraxa
I will be like these feet apart. Relax. One man one hand on the belly another on the back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dance</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/dance/dance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:22:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/dance/dance/</guid>
      <description>Dance Challenge  Dance Challenge - May 2022 Dance Improvement - May 2022   Exercise / Stretching  Dance Challenge Target to finish one challenge per week. By the end of 2 months you will have lot of skills up your sleeve.
Dance Challenge - May 2022   Dance Improvement - May 2022 Body Wave
  Exercise / Stretching Strectching
Daily stretching exercise for improving body movements and body language, making your dance steps sharp and clean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salsa</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/dance/salsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:22:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/dance/salsa/</guid>
      <description>Salsa  Salsa Shines Routine Salsa Dance Routine   Seaon Stylist Bristol  Section 1: Hour One Section 2: Hour Two Section 3   Steps YouTube  Salsa Salsa Shines Routine  Basic, Side Basic, Suzi Q, Side Back Cross, Heel Crusher, Right Turn, Left Turn, 4 Crosses, 4 Taps  Salsa Dance Routine  Basic CBL Basic, CBL, Inside Turn Basic Men&amp;rsquo;s right turn Basic Ladie&amp;rsquo;s outside right turn Hammer Lock  2 ways to come out of hammer lock   Close Hold Open Break  Seaon Stylist Bristol Section 1: Hour One  Basic Side Basic Right Turn Left Turn Front Double Basic: (Shine) Both the basic are happening in front.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>