<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on Naresh Chaurasia</title>
    <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on Naresh Chaurasia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 13:46:55 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Book Summary</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/books/book-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 13:46:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/books/book-summary/</guid>
      <description>Template for Books and Courses My reading strategy has 3 steps:  1. Scanning the territory I am exploring, and defining my learning needs 2. Define clear goals before reading every book 3. Use methods that work for me to connect, distill and chunk the key ideas in any book   Process of learning from books  Step 1: Define your reading radar and learning needs Step 2: Define clear goals for reading every book Step 3: The right methods to connect, distill and chunk ideas     How do I memorize an entire book</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remember The Book You Read</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/books/remember-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 13:46:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/books/remember-book/</guid>
      <description>Remember The Book You Read The 6 SIMPLE HACKS To Remember EVERYTHING You Read  Remember The Book You Read Remember What You Read - How To Memorize What You Read!
 Don&amp;rsquo;t try to memorize as you read but instead highlight or underline the key words Use the Mind Palace technique Create pictures for all the words you have highlighted or underlines See these pictures in your mind palace Segment chapters by using rooms Create pictures for dates if it is a history book      The 6 SIMPLE HACKS To Remember EVERYTHING You Read  Blinkist Mind Map Three Ps Model  Person - The Person in story Principle - What is the Principle I can learn Practical Application - How to turn it into Practical step.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Compound Effect</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/books/compound-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 13:46:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/books/compound-effect/</guid>
      <description>1. The Compound Effect in Action Exercise 1 Write out a few excuses you might be clinging to (e.g., not smart enough, no experience, wrong upbringing, don&amp;rsquo;t have the education, etc.). Decide to make up in hard work and personal development to outcompete anyone—including your old self.
 Not Smart Enough
 Problem: Memory
 Solution: Jonathan Levi, Anki, Harry Lorayne
    Wrong Upbringing
 If I had my parents more available to me teaching the values of people, relationship, money I would be better off.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>