<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Soft Skills on Naresh Chaurasia</title>
    <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/soft-skills/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Soft Skills on Naresh Chaurasia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 13:50:24 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/soft-skills/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/soft-skills/eq1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 13:50:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/soft-skills/eq1/</guid>
      <description>What is Emotional Intelligence EQ V/s IQ The EQ Model Your Brain and EQ How to Improve EQ Mistakes to Avoid in Your EQ Development Using EQ to Manage Relationships. Identifying EQ Around You Common signs of low EQ. Examples of the high EQ Using EQ in Daily Life  Scenario 1 Scenario 2 Scenario 3 Scenario 4 Scenario 5    What is Emotional Intelligence Emotional intelligence is your ability to recognize how your emotions are governing your decisions and your thinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EQ Resolution</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/soft-skills/eq-resolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 13:50:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/soft-skills/eq-resolution/</guid>
      <description>My Mentor, My Hero In 18 years of my career in IT industry, I recently had a privilege to work with one of the finest person, who is now a CTO of an MNC. There is so much to learn from him, in terms of soft skills and technical skills. These are some of his finest qualities that I would like to learn and make it part of my personal and professional life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journaling</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/soft-skills/journaling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 13:50:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/soft-skills/journaling/</guid>
      <description>Journal Keeping Goals and Motivation   Why do you want to keep a journal? Think about why it will help you regardless of the goals you have. We will think about goals in question #3 below.
 Sometime I need someone to talk to. There is lot going on in my personal and professional life. Writing down my thoughts will help me get more clarity, get better perspective in life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Productivity</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/soft-skills/productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 13:50:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/soft-skills/productivity/</guid>
      <description>Productivity</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>