<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Memory Palaces on Naresh Chaurasia</title>
    <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Memory Palaces on Naresh Chaurasia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 17:19:18 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>i20</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/i20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 17:19:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/i20/</guid>
      <description>  https://mechanicalboost.com/car-interior-parts/ https://www.easypacelearning.com/all-lessons/english-level-2/1299-car-parts-vocabulary-list-learn-the-english-words-for-car-parts-using-pictures  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Udemy Content</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/udemy-masters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 17:19:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/udemy-masters/</guid>
      <description>I need around 50+ location in this memory palaces, to create quality content for YouTube, Instagram, Udemy etc. I need to use this learning and start making quality content.
Park 1 Memory Palace  Udemy Masters: Learn Online Course Creation - Unofficial - Phil Ebiner !
 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bajaj Avenger</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/bajaj-avenger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 17:19:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/bajaj-avenger/</guid>
      <description>  I use my avenger very often for most of small trips. It can server as a very good memory palace for my ToDo. I put an item, erase the items. Let me experiment and see how it all goes.
Most of the time it is not more than 10 items, so let me keep it simple.
 Speedometer Right Hand Mirror Accelerator Fuel Tank Rider Seat Passenger Seat </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goal Setting</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/goal-setting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 17:19:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/goal-setting/</guid>
      <description>Mont Vert Walking Track 2  Fence Wall - About your instructor Fence Railing - compartmentalization technique Fence Pillar - Where You Are Green Bench - MAAP Technique Park 2 Pillar - Awareness Park 2 Overhead Railing - Mission Statement Park 1 Overhead Lamp - SMART Garden 1 Drainage Pipeline Penguin Dustbin - Choose at least five Trees / Forest - Time Bench Green Red - Compound Effect Speed Breaker - compartmentalization technique Gas Pipeline - Belief Systems Fire Hose 1 - Your Current Mental Programming Bench Green Color Garden 2 Overhead Railing Garden 2 Pillar Garden 2 Overhead Lamp References      Goal Setting Mastery Course - Himesh Trivedi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intangible Tangible</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/intangible-tangible/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 17:19:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/intangible-tangible/</guid>
      <description> As Bs  As Bs </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Levi</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/jonathan-levi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 17:19:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/jonathan-levi/</guid>
      <description>Living Room Memory Palace  Main Door Front - Progressive Overload Main Door Peep Hole - Pomodoro technique Main Door Back - Memory Main Door Ganpati - Buffers Main Door Magnetic Stopper - Neural Network Wall - neuroplasticity Wall Bulb Holder - Games Wall Switch Board on left - Chunking Samsung TV 65 Inches - Dual Coding and Brute Force Learning Samsung 11.1.4 Subwoofer - Visual Memory &amp;amp; Marker Samsung 11.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Levi Worksheet</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/jonathan-levi-worksheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 17:19:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/jonathan-levi-worksheet/</guid>
      <description>Personal Goals Worksheet Memory Games  Personal Goals Worksheet  Write out 3-5 specific goals that you would like to accomplish… for example, would you like to double your reading speed? Be able to remember the names of 10 new people in a social event? Be able to read 2 new books every month? Make these goals realistic, but also challenging  I would like to be able to read at least 1-2 books every month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory Palaces</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/memory-palaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 17:19:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/memory-palaces/</guid>
      <description>More Memory Palaces A Daily Use Journal / Practial Application Bicycle Bed Room Car Garden Gym Balcony Living Room Study Room - The Original List Subconcious Association Telephone Booth  More Memory Palaces  McDonald&amp;rsquo;s Sound Track Kannu Ki Chai Chai Katta My Body Bike - On The Fly Park H 201 Metafit Gym Wakad Meatfit Gym Pimple Cult Wakad Gym Walking Track Driving Track Meta Fit Multi Fit Cult  A Daily Use Journal / Practial Application  Remember Jonathan Levi using Memory Palace  Bicycle Bed Room  Bed Room Door Light Green Wall Coffee Bottles Wooden Book Unit Speaker Curtain Rod Curtain Balcony Glass Study Table Study Table Drawer Philips Woofer Dark Green Wall Bulb Daat / Loft Fan Bed Head Unit Bed Power Extension  Car  Front Bumper (Outside) Headlight Hood Windshield Windshield Wiper Side Mirror Door Door Handle Wheel / Tire Top / Roof Anteena Trunk Tail Light Number Plate Oil Tank - 15    Dashboard (Inside Front) Mobile Holder Back View Mirror Front Window Glass Front Right Door Bottle Holder Driver&amp;rsquo;s seat Hand Rest Passenter Seat A/c Vent Glove Compartment Music System Steering Wheel Gear    Back Seat File Holder (Inside Back) Back Seat Back Seat Belt Back Seat Store   Garden Gym Balcony Living Room  Jonathan Levi: Speed Reading by Jonathan Levi !</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory Palaces AWS</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/memory-palaces-aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 17:19:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/memory-palaces-aws/</guid>
      <description>Study Room The Original List  IAM    Study Room The Original List  AWS Solution Architect, using Peg System and Memory Palace. A peg will refer to item, which in turn will be placed on Memory Palace.
  Door Outside - Queue, EC2, S3 Door Lock Outside - Regions, Zones, Data Center, Edge Location / Point of Presence   IAM   Door Inside - User drawn on back of door.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Productivity 1.0</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/productivity-1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 17:19:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/productivity-1.0/</guid>
      <description>Mont Vert Walking Track 1  Ramp - Fear Seating Arc - Overwhelm Soil/Earth - Plan Vehilce Mirror - Perfect Tree - Multi-Tasking Fence Wall - Fake Breaks ! Fence Railing - Emotional ! Speed Limit - Email Visitor Parking - Time Managment Overhead Park Fencing / Railing - Spending Time Speed Breaker - Sleep Gas Bank Door - Water Gas Bank Fire Extinguiser - Energy, Mood, Emotional Gas Bank Window - Will Power Lover&amp;rsquo;s Point - Knowing and Doing Basketball Board - The Warren Buffet Productivity Secret Basketball Board Ring - The First and Most Technique Basketball Board Pole Support - Your Productivity Secret Weapon Basketball Court Inner Circle - Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s Law Basketball Court Outer Circle - Themes Basketball Court Center - Resurrecting Your Dead Time   Case Studies  Mind Mapping    Mont Vert Walking Track 1  Productivity and Time Management for the Overwhelmed - Josh Paulsen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Productivity 2.0</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/productivity-2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 17:19:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/productivity-2.0/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  Work on the most important, highest return tasks first and moving away from working on things you really shouldn’t work on.
Introduction If we implement time management practices and properly prioritize our work, we should see significant productivity gains.
If we just manage our time, but haven’t prioritized what we need to do, we could find ourselves being very efficient working on the wrong things. If we have prioritized our tasks, but aren’t good at managing our time, we will know what we have to do, but be frustrated because we just aren’t getting to it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communications</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 13:50:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/memory-palaces/communications/</guid>
      <description>Gateway to Park1 - Mobile Railing on Left - Ears The best communicators in the world are often the best listeners
The Ramp To Garden1 Railing Water Supply Tap </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>