<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Up Skill on Naresh Chaurasia</title>
    <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Up Skill on Naresh Chaurasia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 15:53:08 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Journaling</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/journaling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 15:53:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/journaling/</guid>
      <description>This page will server as a template for Journaling. It will contain structure to write daily, weekly, montly, yearly and life time Journaling.
Becoming Your Life’s Historian  Things you’re working on Relationships New experiences Recent &amp;ldquo;wins&amp;rdquo; Mistakes or missteps Current emotional state How you’re spending time Who you’re surrounded by What you’re planning  Documenting Lessons Learned  &amp;ldquo;Yesterday (or today) I learned…&amp;rdquo;  Chronicling Your Dreams  Describe your dreams Keep journal on bedside table  Morning Pages and Getting It All Out  3 pages of freestyle writing No theme or structure No filters  Your Daily &amp;ldquo;Why&amp;rdquo;  My &amp;lsquo;why&amp;rsquo; for today is… Higher purpose for today&amp;rsquo;s actions  Goals, To-Do&amp;rsquo;s, and Progress Tracking  Today’s 2-3 &amp;ldquo;crucial results&amp;rdquo; Tracking daily habit compliance  Gratitude Journaling  I&amp;rsquo;m grateful for… As many items as you can As detailed as possible  Gratitude Journaling  I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to… As many items as you can As detailed as possible  Training Your Want Muscle  I want… Dream as big as you can Avoid shallow wants  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Da Vinci Resolve</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/da-vinci-resolve/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 11:02:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/da-vinci-resolve/</guid>
      <description>SQ3R System  SQ3R System  During the survey step, which we also call pre-reading, we skim or scan the content before we read it to prepare our mind for the new information. This is thoroughly covered in the coming lectures.  Cut Page Project. A lot is covered in the project.   In the question phase, we ask ourselves questions to improve our motivation, such as why we’re trying to read and what’s in it for us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Templates</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 11:02:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/templates/</guid>
      <description> Technical Template  Sergey Kargopolov Case Study    I need to build / design a system for my learning process. It should cover the following aspects.
Technical Template Sergey Kargopolov Case Study  Mercury Venus https://nareshchaurasia.atlassian.net/browse/ARCH-104  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOGAF</title>
      <link>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/togaf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 11:02:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naresh-chaurasia.github.io/talk2naresh/up-skill/togaf/</guid>
      <description>Jonathan Levi  07.05.2022  This might sound crazy but at least I am able to remember abstract information. Wow !!! It&amp;rsquo;s working    </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>